collegesearch.in 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy - IndiaCollegeSearch

This website – [www.indiacollegesearch.com](http://www.indiacollegesearch.com/) (hereinafter referred to as "Website") is operated and owned by ‘Am Edumedia Private Limited’. We are committed to respecting your online privacy and we recognize your need for protection of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that you share with us. In general, you can visit the website without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information.

This privacy policy sets forth what information we collect from and/or about you and how we use this information.

### Information from Cookies etc

This website utilizes "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A cookie, also known as a web cookie, browser cookie, and HTTP cookie, is a piece of text stored by a user's web browser. When you login to IndiaCollegeSearch.com, we store small cookies in your computer, to provide a better browsing experience for you. You can use your browser to notify you when a cookie is stored or disable cookies altogether.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Uniform Resource Locator (URL), Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses that are used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer information such as version, operating system and platform; connection information such as browser software and version; dates and times that the website is accessed and content that you viewed or searched for on the website. Cookies and other tracking technologies are used by us to improve the Website and your usage experience. We may also use information for analyzing trends and statistics.

### Personal Information

Users of the website are sometimes prompted to provide personal information. The information collected from a user is strictly voluntary and may include but is not restricted to contact information such as the user's name, e-mail address, and phone number.

In order to access certain features and/or services and to make use of the full functionality of the website such as My Shortlisted Colleges, Send Profile, etc. we ask you to register and obtain a personal User Name and Password. You may be prompted to register when you:

1.       Click on the ‘Login’ or ‘Register’ link from the home page or login screens

2.       Click on ‘Add to Shortlist’ link on college profile page

3.       Other unlisted functionality which may be updated and/or incorporated at anytime

The information collected from the registration form that is presented to users when they click on ‘Register’ may include contact information such as the user's name, gender, e-mail address, contact details, description, extracurricular activities and country.

Information collected by the website during registration also includes but is not restricted to Educational Information including exams given, education level, marks, grade or rank obtained and expected year of admission.

This website reserves the right to use the user information compiled during the registration process or otherwise for analysis purposes. The website also reserves the right to provide this information to its business partners / relevant third party for any purpose, including monetary gains.

The website also reserves the right to contact the student based upon the information that they have provided. This contact can be initiated by any possible means on the basis of the information that has been provided by the user at registration or through any other mode of contact.

Any user who is not agreeable to the above policy shall not register themselves with the web site. By registering with the website or by filling up any form requiring user information, the user is deemed to have agreed to this privacy policy of the website.

The terms of this privacy policy are subject to change from time to time without any prior consent or notice.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter your personal information we treat the data as an asset that must be protected and use tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security nor can we guarantee that third parties shall not unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and that other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that you provide. Therefore, although we work hard to protect your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.
